{
"questions":[{
 "question": "Which one is standard way to show popup in Java Script?",
 "answerChoices": ["window.alert('cppbuzz');", "alert('cppbuzz');", "window('cppbuzz');", "alert('cppbuzz')"],
 "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
 "selectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
 "question": "Which method is an alternative of the property location of a window object?",
 "answerChoices": ["submit()", "locate()", "load()", "write()"],
 "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
 "selectedAnswer": ""
 },
 {
 "question": "What is the reason for avoiding the attributes property in the HTML DOM?",
 "answerChoices": ["Found unnecessary", "Attributes donâ€™t have attributes", "Attributes have attributes", "Considered irrelevant"],
 "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
 "selectedAnswer": ""
  },
  {
 "question": "How is everything treated in HTML DOM?",
 "answerChoices": ["Node", "Attributes", "Elements", "Arrays"],
 "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
 "selectedAnswer": ""
  },
  {
 "question": "What is the work of the form control elements in the HTML DOM?",
 "answerChoices": ["User Interface elements", "All the possible elements", "Debugging elements", "Collecting elements"],
 "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
 "selectedAnswer": ""
  },
  {
 "question": "How are the objects organized in the HTML DOM?",
 "answerChoices": ["Class-wise", "Queue", "Hierarchy", "Stack"],
 "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
 "selectedAnswer": ""
  },
  {
 "question": "Which object is the top of the hierarchy?",
 "answerChoices": ["Window Object", "Document Object", "Form Object", "Form Control Elements"],
 "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
 "selectedAnswer": ""
  },
  {
 "question": "Which is the function that calls another function after a time interval?",
 "answerChoices": ["setTimeout()", "setTime()", "callafter()", "timeSet()"],
 "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
 "selectedAnswer": ""
  },
  {
 "question": "Which function is used to clear the timer value?",
 "answerChoices": ["clearTimervalue()", "clearTimeout()", "clear()", "flush(timer)"],
 "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
 "selectedAnswer": ""
  },
  {
 "question": "Which is the property used to position the object in the left of the screen?",
 "answerChoices": ["object.position = left", "object = position.left", "object.style.left", "object.shiftleft"],
 "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
 "selectedAnswer": ""
  }
 ]
}
